Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; KG11366.497 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F68.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; KG11366.498 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F69.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; KG11366.499 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F70.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; KG11366.500 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F71.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; KG11366.501 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F72.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; KG11366.502 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F73.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1879; KG11366.503 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F74.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; KG11366.504 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F75.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; KG11366.505 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F76.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; KG11366.506 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F77.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; KG11366.507 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F78.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; KG11366.508 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F79.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; KG11366.509 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F80.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; KG11366.510 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F81.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1880; KG11366.511 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F82.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881; KG11366.512 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F83.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881; KG11366.513 (Box 64)
  Also identified as: F84.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881; KG11366.514 (Box 65)
  Also identified as: F85.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881; KG11366.515 (Box 65)
  Also identified as: F90.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881; KG11366.516 (Box 65)
  Also identified as: F89.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1881; KG11366.517 (Box 65)
  Also identified as: F88.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1882; KG11366.518 (Box 65)
  Also identified as: F87.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1882; KG11366.519 (Box 65)
  Also identified as: F86.
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1879; KG11366.520 (Box 65)
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1879 to 1880; KG11366.521 (Box 65)
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1880 to 1881; KG11366.522 (Box 65)
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1881; KG11366.523 (Box 65)
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1881 to 1883; KG11366.524 (Box 65)
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1883; KG11366.525 (Box 65)
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1883 to 1884; KG11366.526 (Box 65)
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1884; KG11366.527 (Box 65)
  Also identified as: E9.
- Flexure, Collimation Runs, 1885 to 1886; KG11366.528 (Box 65)
  Also identified as: E10.
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1870; KG11366.529 (Box 65)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1870; KG11366.530 (Box 65)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1871; KG11366.531 (Box 65)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1871; KG11366.532 (Box 65)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1871; KG11366.533 (Box 65)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1871; KG11366.534 (Box 65)
- Zone Circle Readings, 1871; KG11366.535 (Box 65)
  Also identified as: C6'.
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1871; KG11366.536 (Box 65)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1871 to 1872; KG11366.537 (Box 65)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1872; KG11366.538 (Box 65)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.539 (Box 65)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1873; KG11366.540 (Box 65)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1873 to 1874; KG11366.541 (Box 65)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1874; KG11366.542 (Box 66)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1874; KG11366.543 (Box 66)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1874; KG11366.544 (Box 66)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.545 (Box 66)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1875; KG11366.546 (Box 66)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1875; KG11366.547 (Box 66)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1875; KG11366.548 (Box 66)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1875 to 1876; KG11366.549 (Box 66)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1876; KG11366.550 (Box 66)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1876 to 1877; KG11366.551 (Box 66)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1878 to 1879; KG11366.552 (Box 66)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1877 to 1878; KG11366.553 (Box 66)
- Zone Chronograph Records, 1877; KG11366.554 (Box 66)
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1879; KG11366.555 (Box 66)
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1879 to 1880; KG11366.556 (Box 66)
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1880; KG11366.557 (Box 66)
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1880 to 1881; KG11366.558 (Box 66)
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1881; KG11366.559 (Box 66)
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1881 to 1883; KG11366.560 (Box 66)
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1883; KG11366.561 (Box 66)
- Polaris Observations and Reductions, 1883 to 1884; KG11366.562 (Box 66)
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1870; KG11366.563 (Box 66)
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1870 to 1871; KG11366.564 (Box 66)
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871; KG11366.565 (Box 66)
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871; KG11366.566 (Box 66)
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871; KG11366.567 (Box 66)
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871; KG11366.568 (Box 66)
  Also identified as: C6.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871; KG11366.569 (Box 66)
  Also identified as: C7.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871; KG11366.570 (Box 66)
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871; KG11366.571 (Box 67)
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871; KG11366.572 (Box 67)
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871; KG11366.573 (Box 67)
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871; KG11366.574 (Box 67)
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1871 to 1872; KG11366.575 (Box 67)
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1872; KG11366.576 (Box 67)
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.577 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C15.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1873; KG11366.578 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C16.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1873; KG11366.579 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C17.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1873 to 1874; KG11366.580 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C18.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1873; KG11366.581 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C19.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874; KG11366.582 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C20.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874; KG11366.583 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C21.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874; KG11366.584 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C22.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874; KG11366.585 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C23.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874; KG11366.586 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C24.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874; KG11366.587 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C25.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874; KG11366.588 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C26.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.589 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C27.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1875; KG11366.590 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C28.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1875; KG11366.591 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C29.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1875; KG11366.592 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C30.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1875; KG11366.593 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C31.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1875; KG11366.594 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C32.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1875 to 1876; KG11366.595 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C33.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1876; KG11366.596 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C34.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1876; KG11366.597 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C35.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1877; KG11366.598 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C36.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1877; KG11366.599 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C37.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1877; KG11366.600 (Box 67)
  Also identified as: C38.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1877; KG11366.601 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: C39.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1877; KG11366.602 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: C40.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1877 to 1878; KG11366.603 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: C41.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1878; KG11366.604 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: C42.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1878 to 1879; KG11366.605 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: C43.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1883; KG11366.606 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: C44.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1883 to 1884; KG11366.607 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: C45.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1884; KG11366.608 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: C46.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1884 to 1885; KG11366.609 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: C47.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1885; KG11366.610 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: C48.
- Zone Observations and Reductions, 1885; KG11366.611 (Box 68)
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1883; KG11366.612 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: F91.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1883; KG11366.613 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: F92.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1883 to 1884; KG11366.614 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: F96.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1884; KG11366.615 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: F97.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1885; KG11366.616 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: F98.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1885; KG11366.617 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: F99.
- Fundamental Stars Observations and Reductions, 1885 to 1886; KG11366.618 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: F100.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1885; KG11366.619 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: F101.
- Polar Catalog Observations and Reductions, KG11366.620 (Box 68)
  Also identified as: F102.
- Collection of Results in Order of Dates, 1879 to 1881; KG11366.621 (Box 68)
- Readings of the Sun, 1879; KG11366.622 (Box 68)
- Observations of the Sun, 1879; KG11366.623 (Box 68)
- Error of Frodsham 1327, 1903 to 1904; KG11366.624 (Box 69)
  M.F. Michaels and W.W. White.
- Error of Frodsham 1328, 1904 to 1905; KG11366.625 (Box 69)
- Error of Frodsham 1329, 1905; KG11366.626 (Box 69)
- Error of Frodsham 1330, 1905 to 1906; KG11366.627 (Box 69)
- Error of Frodsham 1331, 1906 to 1907; KG11366.628 (Box 69)
  John A. Dunne and W.H..
  W.H. identity uncertain.
- Error of Frodsham 1332, 1907 to 1908; KG11366.629 (Box 69)
  W.H..
- Error of Frodsham 1333, 1908; KG11366.630 (Box 69)
- Error of Frodsham 1334, 1901; KG11366.631 (Box 69)
- Error of Frodsham 1335, 1899 to 1900; KG11366.632 (Box 69)
- Error of Frodsham 1336, 1896 to 1898; KG11366.633 (Box 69)
- Error of Frodsham 1337, 1902 to 1903; KG11366.634 (Box 69)
  M.F. Michaels.
- Chronograph Record, 1879; KG11366.635 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J20.
- Chronograph Record, 1871; KG11366.636 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J3.
  A. McConnel.
  See KG11366.871 and KG11366.872 for J1 and J2.
- Chronograph Record, 1871; KG11366.637 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J4.
- Chronograph Record, 1872; KG11366.638 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J5.
- Chronograph Record, 1872; KG11366.639 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J6.
- Chronograph Record, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.640 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J7.
- Chronograph Record, 1873; KG11366.641 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J8.
- Chronograph Record, 1873 to 1874; KG11366.642 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J9.
- Chronograph Record, 1874; KG11366.643 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J10.
- Chronograph Record, 1874 to 1885; KG11366.644 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J11.
- Chronograph Record, 1875; KG11366.645 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J12.
- Chronograph Record, 1875 to 1876; KG11366.646 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J13.
- Chronograph Record, 1876; KG11366.647 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J14.
- Chronograph Record, 1876; KG11366.648 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J15.
- Chronograph Record, 1876 to 1877; KG11366.649 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J16.
- Chronograph Record, 1877; KG11366.650 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J17.
- Chronograph Record, 1877; KG11366.651 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J18.
- Chronograph Record, 1878 to 1879; KG11366.652 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J19.
- Chronograph Record, 1879 to 1880; KG11366.653 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J21.
- Chronograph Record, 1880; KG11366.654 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J22.
- Chronograph Record, 1880 to 1881; KG11366.655 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J24.
  William A. Rogers and W.V. Brown.
- Chronograph Record, 1881; KG11366.656 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J25.
- Chronograph Record, 1881; KG11366.657 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J26.
- Chronograph Record, 1881 to 1882; KG11366.658 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J27.
- Chronograph Record, 1883; KG11366.659 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J28.
- Chronograph Record, 1883; KG11366.660 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J29.
- Chronograph Record, 1883 to 1884; KG11366.661 (Box 69)
  Also identified as: J30.
- Reports, Meteorological Notes, 1889 to 1894; KG11366.662 (Box 70)
- Reports, Meteorological Notes, 1886 to 1888; KG11366.663 (Box 70)
- Reports, Meteorological Notes, 1883 to 1885; KG11366.664 (Box 70)
- North Pole Reductions, 1897 to 1901; KG11366.665 (Box 70)
- South Pole Reductions, 1896 to 1902; KG11366.666 (Box 70)
- Variable Stars, Computation, 1895 to 1901; KG11366.667 (Box 70)
  Also identified as: T6.
- Tabulation of Observations of Variable Stars, 1903; KG11366.668 (Box 70)
- Memoranda and Reminders, 1896; KG11366.669 (Box 70)
  Also identified as: T9.
- Bright Double Stars, Working Lists, KG11366.670 (Box 70)
  Ann McCormack and William A. Rogers.
- Current Relative and Absolute Estimates, Variable Stars, 1896; KG11366.671 (Box 70)
- Variable Stars, Computation, 1899; KG11366.672 (Box 70)
- Ephemerides of Variables Stars, 1902; KG11366.673 (Box 70)
- Clock Errors, Instrumental Constants, 1871 to 1872; KG11366.674 (Box 70)
  William A. Rogers and A. McConnel.
- Clock Errors, Polar Catalog, Instrumental Constants, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.675 (Box 70)
- Clock Errors, General Catalog, Instrumental Constants, 1874 to 1875; KG11366.676 (Box 70)
- Clock Errors, General Catalog, Instrumental Constants, 1878 to 1879; KG11366.677 (Box 70)
- Clock Errors, General Catalog, Instrumental Constants, 1883; KG11366.678 (Box 70)
- Equator Points, Corrections, 1871 to 1872; KG11366.679 (Box 70)
- Equator Points, Corrections, Flexure Polar Catalog, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.680 (Box 70)
- Equator Points, Corrections, Flexure Constants, 1878; KG11366.681 (Box 70)
- Equator Pt. from Obsns of alpha and lambda, 1876; KG11366.682 (Box 70)
  William A. Rogers and J.E.M..
  J.E.M. identity uncertain.
- Copy of Instrumental Constants 1870-71; Redetermination of deltaT, m h', 1870 to 1878; KG11366.683 (Box 71)
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkoro Coordinates, 1871 to 1872; KG11366.684 (Box 71)
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkoro Coordinates, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.685 (Box 71)
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkoro Coordinates, 1873 to 1874; KG11366.686 (Box 71)
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkoro Coordinates, 1875; KG11366.687 (Box 71)
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkoro Coordinates, 1876; KG11366.688 (Box 71)
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkoro Coordinates, 1877; KG11366.689 (Box 71)
- Instrumental Constants depending on Pulkoro Coordinates, 1877; KG11366.690 (Box 71)
- Final Values of deltaT, m, reg for reduction of Zone Observations, 1870 to 1874; KG11366.691 (Box 71)
- Final Values of deltaT, m, reg for reduction of Zone Observations, 1874 to 1878; KG11366.692 (Box 71)
- Final Values of n and c for reduction of zone observations, 1872 to 1876; KG11366.693 (Box 71)
- Final Values of n and c for reduction of zone observations, 1876 to 1878; KG11366.694 (Box 71)
- Meridian Circle Constants, A, Star Constants, 1872; KG11366.695 (Box 71)
- Instrumental Constants, Star Constants, 1876; KG11366.696 (Box 71)
- Inclination of Declination Wires, 1877; KG11366.697 (Box 71)
  J.F.V..
  J.F.V. identity uncertain.
- DM Places for 155 and 1875; Zone observations, final reductions, KG11366.698 (Box 71)
  Also identified as: J1.
- DM Places for 155 and 1875; Zone observations, final reductions, KG11366.699 (Box 71)
  Also identified as: J2.
- DM Places for 155 and 1875; Zone observations, final reductions, KG11366.700 (Box 71)
- DM Places for 155 and 1875; Zone observations, final reductions, KG11366.701 (Box 71)
- DM Places for 155 and 1875; Zone observations, final reductions, KG11366.702 (Box 71)
- DM Places for 155 and 1875; Zone observations, final reductions, 1883 to 1885; KG11366.703 (Box 71)
- DM list +53 and +54, 1883; KG11366.704 (Box 71)
- DM List +50, +51, +52, KG11366.705 (Box 72)
- Thermometer, Barometer Runs, 1873; KG11366.706 (Box 72)
  Also identified as: D4.
- Thermometer, Barometer Runs, 1875; KG11366.707 (Box 72)
  Also identified as: D8.
- Thermometer, Barometer Runs, 1875 to 1876; KG11366.708 (Box 72)
  Also identified as: D9.
- Thermometer, Barometer Runs, 1876; KG11366.709 (Box 72)
  Also identified as: D10.
- Planet and Satellite Observations, KG11366.710 (Box 72)
  Also identified as: R14.
- Star Observations, 1877; KG11366.711 (Box 72)
- Star Observations, 1877 to 1878; KG11366.712 (Box 72)
- Star Observations, 1869; KG11366.713 (Box 72)
  Also identified as: R27.
- Meteorological Record, 1880 to 1882; KG11366.714 (Box 72)
  Also identified as: R67.
- Notes on SMP, 1892; KG11366.715 (Box 72)
- Micrometer Level, 1877; KG11366.716 (Box 72)
- Reduction of Observations by Schmidt by Reed, KG11366.717 (Box 72)
- Early lists of gaseous neb, stars Pec. Specctra, 1880; KG11366.718 (Box 72)
- Discussion of H.A. 24, group MP according to DM, KG11366.719 (Box 72)
- Discussion of H.A. 24, group MP according to DM, KG11366.720 (Box 72)
- Stars and Cluster, Lists with X plates entered, 1899; KG11366.721 (Box 72)
- Double Stars, KG11366.722 (Box 72)
- Double Stars, KG11366.723 (Box 72)
- Asteroid Zone Book, KG11366.724 (Box 72)
- Eros Book, 1893; KG11366.725 (Box 72)
- Eros Book, 1876; KG11366.726 (Box 72)
- Zone Stars, 1870; KG11366.727 (Box 72)
- Russian Transit, KG11366.728 (Box 72)
  Also identified as: U4.
- Zone Circle Recordings, 1870; KG11366.729 (Box 72)
  Also identified as: U5.
- Zone Circle Recordings, KG11366.730 (Box 72)
  Also identified as: U6.
- Zone Circle Recordings, 1871; KG11366.731 (Box 72)
  Also identified as: U7.
- D.M. List, KG11366.732 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U10.
- Borton's notebook, 1880; KG11366.733 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U.
  Martha C. Borton.
- Record of work by D.B. Pratt, 1883 to 1884; KG11366.734 (Box 73)
  D.B. Pratt.
- Stars(zone) needing re-examination of chronograph sheets, 1871; KG11366.735 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U14.
- Stars to be re-observed, KG11366.736 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U15.
- Star places, 1875 to 1876; KG11366.737 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U16.
- K'K D D', KG11366.738 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U17.
- K'K D D', KG11366.739 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U18.
- Zero stars, Red to apparent place, KG11366.740 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U19.
- Table for reductions, KG11366.741 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U20.
- Fundamental Stars, Ephemerides, 1879; KG11366.742 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U22.
- Fundamental Stars, Ephemerides, 1879; KG11366.743 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U23.
- Working Lists, Fundamental Stars, 1879; KG11366.744 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U24.
- Working Lists, Fundamental Stars, 1879; KG11366.745 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U25.
- Longitude Campaign - Observations and Reductions, 1872 to 1873; KG11366.746 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U27.
- Miscellaneous Observations, 1881; KG11366.747 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U28.
- Montreal Cambridge Longitude Observations, 1883; KG11366.748 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U30.
- Longitude Campaign: Montreal- Cambridge, 1883; KG11366.749 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U31.
- General Catalog List, KG11366.750 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U34.
- [Book], 1875; KG11366.751 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U37.
  Contents/title unknown.
- [Missing], KG11366.752 (Box 73)
- Chronograph Record, KG11366.753 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U40.
- List of Polar Stars with Dates of Observations, 1885; KG11366.754 (Box 73)
  Also identified as: U41.
- Flexure Colimation Runs, 1880; KG11366.755 (Box 73)
  W.C..
  W.C. identity uncertain.
- Investigation of Circle Observations, 1879; KG11366.756 (Box 73)
- Longitude of Circle Errors, 1881; KG11366.757 (Box 73)
- Investigation of Circle - Discussion, KG11366.758 (Box 73)
- Investigation of Errors of West Circle from Stops, 1884; KG11366.759 (Box 73)
- Investigation of Circle, 1877 to 1879; KG11366.760 (Box 73)
- Investigation of Circle Observations, 1871 to 1879; KG11366.761 (Box 73)
- Investigation of Errors of West Circle from Stops, 1884 to 1885; KG11366.762 (Box 73)
- Investigation of Errors of West Circle from Stops, 1885; KG11366.763 (Box 74)
- Investigation of Errors of West Circle from Stops, 1885; KG11366.764 (Box 74)
- Investigation of Errors of West Circle from Stops, 1885; KG11366.765 (Box 74)
- Investigation of Circle Observations, 1879; KG11366.766 (Box 74)
- Jupiter Eclipses and Variable Stars, 1900; KG11366.767 (Box 74)
- Jupiter Eclipses and Variable Stars, 1902; KG11366.768 (Box 74)
- Jupiter Eclipses and Variable Stars, 1894; KG11366.769 (Box 74)
- Jupiter Eclipses and Variable Stars, 1903; KG11366.770 (Box 74)
  R.W.L..
  R.W.L. identity uncertain.
- Variable Stars Zone P.M. XI, KG11366.771 (Box 74)
- Various Stars Zone P.M. XII, KG11366.772 (Box 74)
- Arequipa Time Book No.1, 1891 to 1892; KG11366.773 (Box 74)
- Chronograph comparisons, 1892; KG11366.774 (Box 74)
  John A. Dunne and W.W..
  W.W identity uncertain.
- Comparison of Waltham Clock with South clock, 1878; KG11366.775 (Box 74)
- Error of Sidereal Clock, 1908; KG11366.776 (Box 74)
- Error of Sidereal Clock, 1913; KG11366.777 (Box 74)
- Error of Sidereal Clock, 1911; KG11366.778 (Box 74)
- Error of Sidereal Clock, 1910; KG11366.779 (Box 74)
- Observations, 1876; KG11366.780 (Box 74)
- Time book, 1875; KG11366.781 (Box 74)
- Time book, 1874; KG11366.782 (Box 74)
- Time book, 1874; KG11366.783 (Box 74)
- Time book, 1874; KG11366.784 (Box 74)
- Time Service (Clock Errors), 1879; KG11366.785 (Box 74)
- Clock Errors, 1878; KG11366.786 (Box 75)
- Time Service, 1888 to 1890; KG11366.787 (Box 75)
- Time Service, 1890 to 1891; KG11366.788 (Box 75)
- Time Service, 1891; KG11366.789 (Box 75)
- Time Service and Russian Transit, 1877; KG11366.790 (Box 75)
- Check Readings of Sheets of Observations for longitude, 1871; KG11366.791 (Box 75)
  H. Gannett.
- Russian Transit, 1883; KG11366.792 (Box 75)
- Time Service, Clock Errors and Russian Transit, 1877; KG11366.793 (Box 75)
- Time Service, Clock Errors and Russian Transit, 1877; KG11366.794 (Box 75)
- Time Service, Clock Comparison, 1881; KG11366.795 (Box 75)
- Level of East Transit, 1877; KG11366.796 (Box 75)
- Time Service, 1887 to 1888; KG11366.797 (Box 75)
- Time Service, 1882 to 1883; KG11366.798 (Box 75)
- Time Service, 1892 to 1894; KG11366.799 (Box 75)
- Time Service, 1880; KG11366.800 (Box 75)
  Harriet Wace.
- Time Service Clock Comparisons, 1879 to 1880; KG11366.801 (Box 75)
- Time Service Clock Comparisons, 1878 to 1879; KG11366.802 (Box 75)
- References book: Stars, Asteroids, etc. under observation, KG11366.803 (Box 75)